<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="http://www.eia.gov/rss/rss.xsl" type="text/xsl" media="screen"?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>EIA: This Week in Petroleum</title>
      <link>http://www.eia.gov/oog/info/twip/twip.asp</link>
      <description>U.S. petroleum fuels prices and volumns nationally and by region.</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
 <image> <title>EIA logo</title>
         <url>http://www.eia.gov/global/images/logos/eia_logo_250.png</url>
         <link>http://www.eia.gov/</link>
         <description>US Energy Information Administration</description>
      </image>
	  

	  
<item> <title>Average crude oil prices forecast to rise as markets move toward balance (1/11/2017)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2017/170111/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>The U.S. Energy Information Administration's (EIA) January Short-Term Energy Outlook (STEO) forecasts benchmark North Sea Brent and West Texas Intermediate (WTI) to average $53 per barrel (b) and $52/b, respectively, in 2017, close to their levels during the last three weeks of 2016. Average forecast prices rise to $56/b and $55/b, respectively, in 2018. ...</description>	   
      </item>   
		  
	

	
	  
<item> <title>EIA now using near-real-time export data to provide better weekly petroleum consumption statistics (1/5/2017)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2017/170105/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>Starting with the August 31 release of the Weekly Petroleum Status Report (WPSR), EIA is now publishing weekly export and petroleum consumption estimates based on near-real-time export data provided by U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP). ...</description>	   
      </item>   
		  
	

	
	  
<item> <title>U.S. average regular gasoline and diesel retail prices climb (12/29/2016)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2016/161229/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>The U.S. average regular gasoline retail price rose almost five cents from the previous week to $2.31 per gallon on December 26, up nearly 28 cents from the same time last year. The Midwest price rose nine cents to $2.28 per gallon and the Rocky Mountain price rose four cents to $2.18 per gallon. The West Coast and the Gulf Coast prices each rose three cents to $2.59 per gallon and $2.08 per gallon, respectively, while the East Coast price rose two cents to $2.31 per gallon. ...</description>	   
      </item>   
		  
	

	
<item> <title>Strategic Petroleum Reserve sales under recently enacted laws are expected to start in January 2017 (12/21/2016)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2016/161221/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>The Department of Energy's (DOE) Office of Fossil Energy recently announced that it will sell crude oil from the Strategic Petroleum Reserve (SPR) as early as January 2017. The announcement came after a Continuing Resolution that included a provision for DOE to sell up to $375.4 million in crude oil from the SPR was enacted into law earlier this month. This sale is the first of several planned sales totaling nearly 190 million barrels (Figure 1) during fiscal years 2017 through 2025. These sales reflect provisions in several recent statutes, including sections 403 and 404 of the Bipartisan Budget Act of 2015 (BBA), the Fixing America's Surface Transportation Act (FAST Act), which became law in December 2015, and the 21st Century Cures Act (Cures Act), which became law earlier this month. ...</description>	   
      </item>   
		  
		  

	 
	  
	  
	  
	  </channel>	  

</rss>
 
