<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="http://www.eia.gov/rss/rss.xsl" type="text/xsl" media="screen"?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>EIA: This Week in Petroleum</title>
      <link>http://www.eia.gov/oog/info/twip/twip.asp</link>
      <description>U.S. petroleum fuels prices and volumns nationally and by region.</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
 <image> <title>EIA logo</title>
         <url>http://www.eia.gov/global/images/logos/eia_logo_250.png</url>
         <link>http://www.eia.gov/</link>
         <description>US Energy Information Administration</description>
      </image>
	  

	  
<item> <title>Mexican gasoline market reforms could influence U.S. gasoline export trends (1/25/2017)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2017/170125/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>The Mexican government is in the process of opening its gasoline and diesel markets to outside competition and replacing government-set prices with market-based prices. Last year, Mexico began allowing entities other than the state-owned company Petróleos Mexicanos (Pemex) to import gasoline and diesel and open retail stations. These changes followed previous energy sector reforms that ended Pemex’s upstream monopoly and opened the oil and natural gas sectors to foreign direct investment. Although Mexico is a large crude oil producer, it relies heavily on imports of gasoline from the United States to meet domestic demand. Therefore, the outcome of gasoline market reforms in Mexico may have significant implications for the sale of U.S.-produced gasoline. ...</description>
		 </item>  
		  
	
	
	  
<item> <title>Hydrocarbon gas liquids becoming a key factor in overall liquid fuel balance changes (1/19/2017)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2017/170119/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>Hydrocarbon gas liquids (HGL)-a group of products that includes ethane, propane, normal butane, isobutane, natural gasoline, and refinery olefins-have traditionally accounted for only minor changes in global liquid fuels production and consumption balances. However, HGL, and in particular ethane, is becoming a significant factor in expected year-over-year changes in global liquid fuels balances. ...</description>	   
      </item>   
		  
	

	
	  
<item> <title>Average crude oil prices forecast to rise as markets move toward balance (1/11/2017)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2017/170111/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>The U.S. Energy Information Administration's (EIA) January Short-Term Energy Outlook (STEO) forecasts benchmark North Sea Brent and West Texas Intermediate (WTI) to average $53 per barrel (b) and $52/b, respectively, in 2017, close to their levels during the last three weeks of 2016. Average forecast prices rise to $56/b and $55/b, respectively, in 2018. ...</description>	   
      </item>   
		  
	

	
	  
<item> <title>EIA now using near-real-time export data to provide better weekly petroleum consumption statistics (1/5/2017)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2017/170105/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>Starting with the August 31 release of the Weekly Petroleum Status Report (WPSR), EIA is now publishing weekly export and petroleum consumption estimates based on near-real-time export data provided by U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP). ...</description>	   
      </item>   
		  
	
		  

	 
	  
	  
	  
	  </channel>	  

</rss>
 
