<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="http://www.eia.gov/rss/rss.xsl" type="text/xsl" media="screen"?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>EIA: This Week in Petroleum</title>
      <link>http://www.eia.gov/oog/info/twip/twip.asp</link>
      <description>U.S. petroleum fuels prices and volumns nationally and by region.</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
 <image> <title>EIA logo</title>
         <url>http://www.eia.gov/global/images/logos/eia_logo_250.png</url>
         <link>http://www.eia.gov/</link>
         <description>US Energy Information Administration</description>
      </image>
	  

	  
<item> <title>Hydrocarbon gas liquids by rail data adds transparency to rapidly changing markets (2/8/2017)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2017/170208/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>EIA recently added information on rail movements of propane, propylene, normal butane, and isobutane to its monthly petroleum data. These four products make up the majority of hydrocarbon gas liquids (HGL) moved by rail. This data adds transparency to market supply and demand dynamics for regions that are a source or destination for these products. Meanwhile, the growth in HGL-by-rail highlights market changes resulting from increased U.S. HGL production. ...</description>
		 </item>  	  
      
	  

	  
<item> <title>U.S. heating oil and propane prices higher than same time last year (2/2/2017)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2017/170202/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>Despite most of the country experiencing, on average, a relatively warm winter so far, higher crude oil prices have contributed to higher heating oil prices and strong export demand for propane has resulted in higher prices for that fuel as well. Last winter, unseasonably warm temperatures and falling crude oil prices combined to keep expenditures for winter heating fuels lower than historical averages. The latest EIA Short-Term Energy Outlook (STEO) projects U.S. average heating oil and propane expenditures to increase 36% and 23%, respectively, compared with last winter, but both are still projected to be lower than average expenditures over the past 10 winters. Heating oil expenditures are expected to be $475 (26%) lower than the average expenditures of the previous 10 winters, and propane $14 (0.7%) lower. ...</description>
		 </item>  
		  
	
	
	  
<item> <title>Mexican gasoline market reforms could influence U.S. gasoline export trends (1/25/2017)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2017/170125/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>The Mexican government is in the process of opening its gasoline and diesel markets to outside competition and replacing government-set prices with market-based prices. Last year, Mexico began allowing entities other than the state-owned company Petróleos Mexicanos (Pemex) to import gasoline and diesel and open retail stations. These changes followed previous energy sector reforms that ended Pemex’s upstream monopoly and opened the oil and natural gas sectors to foreign direct investment. Although Mexico is a large crude oil producer, it relies heavily on imports of gasoline from the United States to meet domestic demand. Therefore, the outcome of gasoline market reforms in Mexico may have significant implications for the sale of U.S.-produced gasoline. ...</description>
		 </item>  
		  
	
	
	  
<item> <title>Hydrocarbon gas liquids becoming a key factor in overall liquid fuel balance changes (1/19/2017)</title>
       <link>http://www.eia.gov/petroleum/weekly/archive/2017/170119/includes/analysis_print.cfm</link>
         <pubDate>############# EST</pubDate>
         <description>Hydrocarbon gas liquids (HGL)-a group of products that includes ethane, propane, normal butane, isobutane, natural gasoline, and refinery olefins-have traditionally accounted for only minor changes in global liquid fuels production and consumption balances. However, HGL, and in particular ethane, is becoming a significant factor in expected year-over-year changes in global liquid fuels balances. ...</description>	   
      </item>   
		  
	
		  
	
		  

	 
	  
	  
	  
	  </channel>	  

</rss>
 
